Sam Peterson

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Phone

+11 230 909 8298

Email

peterson2020@fakeemail.com

Address

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies

June 2017 - July 2020

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science
Honours

July 2020 - Present

SKILL

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

ABOUT ME

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Google Inc

January 2017 - August 2017

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was insynch with everything
- Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in synch

TESTER

Microsoft

July 2019 - Present

- Mantain server
- Provide and facilitate end user assistance
- Maintain computer parifinalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in synch

REFERENCE

Kutlo Sek, Google Inc

Senior Developer

Email: kutlosek@fakeemail.com

Pat Robertson, TBN Television

Producer

Email: patrobert@fakemail.com